start with a pentagon of area one take a
scaled copy that's size 1 six and place
it in the center leaving the outer ring
of size 56 we can cut the outer ring
into five congruent trapezoids each with
Area 1 six when we shade all five we've
shaded 5 six of the Pentagon do this
again on the inner Pentagon of Area 1 16
shading 56 of the 1 16 area therefore
shading a total area of 5 over 6^ SAR we
can repeat this process over and over
again each time shading 5 over 6 to the
N of the outer Pentagon if we can
continue this process indefinitely that
means if we consider a limiting process
we can look at the limiting shape and
the limiting shape is the filled
Pentagon therefore the Shaded area given
by the infinite sum matches the area of
the Pentagon which is one one
interpretation of this is that point
five repeating in base 6 is equal to 1
another one is that 5 * the infinite sum
of the positive powers of 1 six equals 1
or that the infinite sum of the positive
powers of 1 16 is 1/5